// Test Questions
let beginnerLevel = [
    {
        question: "What is the opposite of dangerous?",
        1: "easy",
        2: "comfortable",
        3: "safe",
        answer: "3",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "I have been to the cinema yesterday.",
        2: "I was at the cinema yesterday.",
        3: "I was been at the cinema yesterday.",
        answer: "2",
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following modals doesn't have a short form?",
        1: "cannot",
        2: "may not",
        3: "need not",
        answer: "2",
    },

    {
        question: "What is a busker?",
        1: "a bus driver",
        2: "a musical instrument",
        3: "a street musician",
        answer: "3",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "You have to learn these words at heart.",
        2: "You have to learn these words by heart.",
        3: "You have to learn these words for heart.",
        answer: "2",
    },

    {
        question: "Who's the boss of a tennis match?",
        1: "leader",
        2: "manager",
        3: "umpire",
        answer: "3",
    },

    {
        question: "Which answers to the following question are correct? Whose book is it?",
        1: "It's mine.",
        2: "It's my.",
        3: "It's me.",
        answer: "1",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "Peter wanted his mother to help him.",
        2: "Peter wanted his mother to helps him.",
        3: "Peter wanted that his mother helps him.",
        answer: "1",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "I didn't get some apples.",
        2: "I haven't got any time.",
        3: "There's any milk in the fridge.",
        answer: "2",
    },

    {
        question: "Which question is correct?",
        1: "Can you give me an advice?",
        2: "Can you give me some advice?",
        3: "Can you give me some advices?",
        answer: "Can you give me some advice?",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "The telephone is calling.",
        2: "The telephone is calling.",
        3: "The telephone is ringing.",
        4: "The telephone is sounding.",
        answer: "The telephone is ringing.",
    },

    {
        question: "What is the opposite of to buy?",
        1: "to lend",
        2: "to sell",
        3: "to take",
        answer: "to sell",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "He went to school yesterday.",
        2: "He went yesterday to school.",
        3: "Yesterday he has gone to school.",
        answer: "He went to school yesterday.",
    },

    {
        question: "What is the answer to this question? I like tennis.",
        1: "I am also.",
        2: "So do I.",
        3: "So like I.",
        answer: "So do I.",
    },

    {
        question: " Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "My mother works half-time at Burger King.",
        2: "My mother works part-time at Burger King.",
        3: "My mother works spare time at Burger King.",
        answer: "My mother works part-time at Burger King.",
    },
];


let intermediateLevel = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following sentences is written in Passive?",
        1: "He is reading a book.",
        2: "I am given a book.",
        3: "I give him a book.",
        answer: "I am given a book.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "I look forward at seeing you soon.",
        2: "I look forward for seeing you soon.",
        3: "I look forward to seeing you soon.",
        answer: "I look forward to seeing you soon.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following sentences is written in Passive?",
        1: "A house is built.",
        2: "She goes to school.",
        3: "They read a book.",
        answer: "A house is built.",
    },

    {
        question: "What is the opposite of now?",
        1: "again",
        2: "soon",
        3: "then",
        answer: "then",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "The policeman made me open the suitcase.",
        2: "The policeman made me opening the suitcase.",
        3: "The policeman made me to open the suitcase.",
        answer: "The policeman made me open the suitcase.",
    },

    {
        question: "Complete this phrase: As fresh as",
        1: "a daisy",
        2: "milk",
        3: "Spring",
        answer: "As fresh as a daisy",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "She is always complaining about her father.",
        2: "She is always complaining of her father.",
        3: "She is always complaining to her father",
        answer: "She is always complaining about her father.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which two words sound the same?",
        1: "feat, feet",
        2: "fit, feed",
        3: "fit, feet",
        answer: "feat, feet",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "Albert Einstein was a great physician.",
        2: "In my meaning rats are nice animals.",
        3: "The Yukon is the longest river in Alaska.",
        answer: "The Yukon is the longest river in Alaska.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which is the most polite phrase when telephoning?",
        1: "Hang on.",
        2: "Hold on.",
        3: "Just a moment, please.",
        answer: "Just a moment, please.",
    },

    {
        question: "What do you call a person who you can trust and depend on at all times?",
        1: "absent-minded",
        2: "impulsive",
        3: "reliable",
        answer: "reliable",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "There isn't a one computer in this office.",
        2: "There isn't a single computer in this office.",
        3: "There isn't an only computer in this office.",
        answer: "There isn't a single computer in this office.",
    },

    {
        question: "When you want to buy a house in England, the money you borrow is called:",
        1: "deposit",
        2: "loan",
        3: "mortgage",
        answer: "mortgage",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: " I'm rather short at money.",
        2: "I'm rather short of money.",
        3: "I'm rather short on money.",
        answer: "I'm rather short of money.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which two words sound the same?",
        1: "well, will",
        2: "wheel, we'll",
        3: "will, we'll",
        answer: "we'll",
    },
];

let advancedLevel = [
    {
        question: "Which word is closest in meaning to these three: love, like, enjoy?",
        1: "adore",
        2: "hope",
        3: "want",
        answer: "adore",
    },

    {
        question: "Where does a porter work?",
        1: "in the library",
        2: "in the supermarket",
        3: "at the station",
        answer: "at the station",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "At this time tomorrow I take my driving test.",
        2: "At this time tomorrow I will be taking my driving test.",
        3: "At this time tomorrow I will take my driving test.",
        answer: "At this time tomorrow I will be taking my driving test.",
    },

    {
        question: "What do you call a person who was born in Norwich?",
        1: "a native of Norwich",
        2: "a resident of Norwich",
        3: "an inhabitant of Norwich",
        answer: "a native of Norwich",
    },

    {
        question: "What is a synonym to rude?",
        1: "brave",
        2: "impolite",
        3: "stupid",
        answer: "impolite",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "I want to have a word with you before you go.",
        2: "I want to have a word with you before you will go.",
        3: "I want to have a word with you before you will have gone.",
        answer: "I want to have a word with you before you go.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "The rent is to be paid at advance.",
        2: "The rent is to be paid for advance.",
        3: "The rent is to be paid in advance.",
        answer: "The rent is to be paid in advance.",
    },

    {
        question: "The middle of an apple which we don't eat is called the:",
        1: "centre",
        2: "core",
        3: "heart",
        answer: "core",
    },

    {
        question: "The back end of a ship is called:",
        1: "the deck",
        2: "the mast",
        3: "the stern",
        answer: "the stern",
    },

    {
        question: "Complete this phrase: hale and",
        1: "fit",
        2: "healthy",
        3: "hearty",
        answer: "hearty",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
    1: "This film is at far the best one he's ever made.",
        2: "This film is by far the best one he's ever made.",
        3: "This film is so far the best one he's ever made.",
        answer: "This film is by far the best one he's ever made.",
    },

    {
        question: "Which sentence is correct?",
        1: "I'm going to do my homework.",
        2: "Do the beds",
        3: "She often does some coffee.",
        answer: "I'm going to do my homework.",
    },
];
















